http://sixated.com/privacy/

Privacy - Sixated
Sixated
Top 10 lists are so last year
Follow Us:
Home Page
Top 6 PostsThe 6 Handbags Every Woman Should Own 6 BB Creams for Flawless-Looking Skin The 6 Best Drugstore Mascaras of All Time The 6 Best Fashion Tips Ever Top 6 Fashion Trends for Fall 2015 6 Ways to Wear Boyfriend Jeans with Boots
The 6 Best Drugstore Mascaras of All Time
Top 6 Fashion Trends for Fall 2015
6 BB Creams for Flawless-Looking Skin
The 6 Best Fashion Tips Ever
Privacy
we respect your privacy and will never share your email address with any third party
This email list is hosted and managed by MailerMailer.com. To report any abuse or violations of this Email List Privacy Policy, please send email to abuse@mailermailer.com and attach an unedited copy of the email message that you feel was sent to you in error or without your permission. Include all header information so that MailerMailer.com can trace origin of the message. Also include any notes or other information that you feel are pertinent.
Email List Information Collection
For each visitor that signs up for our email list, we collect only the information that is requested on the list signup form. Required fields are denoted with an asterisk (*). Our web servers may collect the domain name or IP address of visitors to our web page(s). Unless otherwise stated on our web site, we collect the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email and information volunteered by you such as but not limited to list signup information, survey information, and/or site registrations. We also may collect clickstream information. In our email messages to you which are distributed through this list, we may have information from third party providers for products and services which may be advertised or promoted within messages we send to you from this email list–the privacy policies of those third-party provider sites govern the method by which they collect and use such information.
Use of Web Site Information Collected
The information we collect may be used to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base and those of the MailerMailer.com email list management service so that we and MailerMailer can improve content and services and provide aggregate information to potential advertisers (no individual information is provided to any third-party without your consent), to customize the content and/or layout of our email messages or pages for each individual visitor, to notify you about updates to our web site and services, to send you our opt-in e-mail newsletter(s), to provide you with the services for which you signed-up or registered, which may include sending service disruption notices or other service- or product-related information via email, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without your consent. We may share collected information with another company in the event that we merge with or are acquired by another company. Upon request, we will provide you with the information (e.g., email address, name, etc.) that we maintain about you.
E-mail and Direct Response Contact
If you subscribed to our e-mail newsletter(s) but do not want to receive it in the future, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions contained in the newsletter(s).
Cookies
We, and some of our partners who provide some of the services and products on our site, may use cookies to record session information, such as record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when you return to our site, and customize web page or email message content based on your browser type or other information. Cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.
The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies.
Security
We and MailerMailer.com, providers of the email list management service used for this list, strive to maintain appropriate security measures in our respective physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you for being part of our email list. Although we and MailerMailer take reasonable measures to secure our data, we cannot guarantee that the measures taken are or will remain adequate. Since we may include links from messages sent to the email list to other companies’ web sites, please refer to the privacy policies of those sites for information on how they handle security for information they collect.
Changes to Email List Privacy Policy
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Email List Privacy Policy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to this Email List Privacy Policy page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of our list.
Third Party Advertising
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
The Latest:6 Supercharged Anti-Aging Serums for All Budgets 6 Life-Changing Video Tutorials for How to Tie a Scarf 6 BFF-Worthy Baby Gifts Under $50
Follow Us:
© Sixated 2020
buy accutane
